999dice.com 2006-06-17

# Network - 999 Network

### Privacy Policy

#### 1\. General

1.1 We are committed to our protection of your privacy. No information collected by us on the site will be sold, rented or loaned except as expressly stated in the Privacy Policy and consented to by you.

1.2 We will use all reasonable endeavours to ensure that all personal information given to us through the site will only be held and used with care and in accordance with the Privacy Policy and the Data Protection Act 1998.

#### 2\. Use of Information

2.1 We will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided, for example, at the time of registration. This data is referred to in the Privacy Policy as 'personal information'.

2.2 The information collected will be used by us to process your requests for information or advice as well as to further develop the site to be useful to you and enable us to provide further services on the site in the future. We may also wish to provide you with news and information about other services that may be of interest to you.

2.3 We may share non-personal aggregate statistics (group) data about visitors to the site, sales and traffic patterns with other parties. However, we do not sell or share any information about you as an individual user of the site unless you agree to us doing so.

2.4 At every point on the site where such personal information is collected, we give you the option to tell us if you do not want your personal information to be used in the way. If at any later stage you decide you would rather not receive such information please contact us immediately by email on 

#### 3\. 'Cookies'

3.1 We use "cookies" on the site. Cookies are small text files on your computer.

3.2 Although our cookies contain identifying information they do not contain any information that identifies you personally, but they allow us to provide certain features and to recognise you when you return to our site.

3.3 If you do not want to accept a cookie when you visit our site you should be able to change the settings on your browser to disable this function. Alternatively, please contact your Internet Service Provider.

#### 4\. Links to other sites

4.1 We may from time to time establish relationships with other companies or organisations that will enable you to access the websites of such companies or organisations directly from our site.

4.2 Each individual company or organisation operates its own privacy policy regarding the sale of personal information and the use of cookies.

4.3 If you have a particular interest or concern regarding the way your personal information will be used then you are advised to read the privacy policy on the relevant site, which will supersede our privacy policy. In the same way, if you have visited our site by way of a link from another site, our privacy policy will prevail.

4.4 We will try to provide you with links to high quality, reputable sites which we believe will be of interest and relevant to you, but please note that such third party sites are not under our control and we do not contribute to the content of such websites.

4.5 When you click through to these sites you leave the area controlled by us. We cannot accept responsibility for any issues arising in connection with either the third party's use of your data, the site content or the services offered to you by these sites.

#### 5\. Your Rights

5.1 In addition to these policies your personal information is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act 1998.

5.2 Under this Act we will use our reasonable endeavours to process any data we hold about you in a lawful and fair manner.

5.3 We will use our reasonable endeavours to keep your personal information securely to prevent unauthorised access by third parties.

5.4 On a sale or merger of our business, your personal information may be disclosed to our advisers, to any prospective purchaser or merging entity (including any of their advisers) and ultimately, to the actual purchaser of our business or entity which merges with our business.

5.5 We cannot guarantee that when, subject to first receiving your consent, we transfer your personal information to third parties in other jurisdictions, such jurisdictions operate an adequate or equivalent level of data protection as prevails in England & Wales.

#### 6\. Policy Changes

6.1 Any changes to the privacy policy made by us will be posted here and will take effect immediately. The policy was last updated on 25th October 2002.

6.2 If you have any additional queries about privacy, please send an email to [privacy@999network.com](mailto:privacy@999network.com?subject=Privacy%20policy "Privacy email address") and we will endeavour to help.
